{"data":[{"question":"We _____ (buy) them here yesterday.","a":"buyed","b":"bought","c":"buied","answer":"2","explain":"- Buy -> bought(irregular verb)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"6"},{"question":"She _____ (get) up at 6.30 last morning.","a":"get","b":"got","c":"gotten","answer":"2","explain":"- Get -> got (irregular verb)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"6"},{"question":"My mother _____ (choose) this hotel.","a":"chose","b":"choosed","c":"chosen","answer":"1","explain":"- Choose -> chose (irregular verb)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"6"},{"question":"They _____ (not fly) to New York.","a":"didn't fly","b":"didn't flew","c":"didn't flied","answer":"1","explain":"- Negative: did not\/didn't + infinitive.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"6"},{"question":"He _____ (ride) yesterday?","a":"Did he ride","b":"Did he rided","c":"Did he ried","answer":"1","explain":"- The question form : Did + S + V...?","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"6"},{"question":"We _____ (drink) wine last night.","a":"drinked","b":"drank","c":"drunk","answer":"2","explain":"- Drink -> drank (irregular verb)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"6"},{"question":"She _____ (lend) you enough money?","a":"Did she lent","b":"Did she lend","c":"Did she lended","answer":"2","explain":"- Interrogative: Did + subject + infinitive?","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"6"},{"question":"His wife _____ (come) at 8.00 this morning.","a":"come","b":"came","c":"comed","answer":"2","explain":"- Come -> came (irregular verb)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"6"},{"question":"They _____ (not spend) it all.","a":"didn't spend","b":"didn't spent","c":"didn't spended","answer":"1","explain":"- Negative: did not\/didn't + infinitive.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"6"},{"question":"His son _____ (write) a novel.","a":"writed","b":"wrote","c":"written","answer":"2","explain":"- Write -> wrote (irregular verb)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"6"}]}